Good afternoon, people.
Happy Wednesday to you.
I think it's Wednesday, at least.
Maybe it's Tuesday.
No, it's Tuesday.
Fuck, I never get it right.
What's up?
Disclaimer, I feel a little under the weather today.
But I really wanted to play Isaac, and my plan was to play Isaac.
So I'm playing Isaac.
Follow your dreams.
My first coffee of today.
Didn't get any this morning.
Jackie didn't allow me to.
She said, Oliver, no more coffee.
Not good for you.
But she's wrong, it is good for me.
Because I feel so good now.
What's up?
You're here.
I guess.
Yes, I've heard of... I don't know if you're joking at this point.
Yes, I've heard of Mugenics.
Only every time I stream.
But yes, I am going to play it one day.
I don't know when, but at some point.
Day three of asking to install hit counter mod.
What is that even?
Let me actually give that a Google.
Let me just see what that is.
Isaac hit counter mod.
That's a counter near your health to display the total amount of hits in a run.
Oh, I mean, that's kind of that's kind of cool, I guess.
I guess I could install that.
I guess it's just interesting statistics.
Oh, I something I need to remember today.
People in the YouTube comments pointed this out.
The game is apparently very dark on YouTube because of the compression or something.
I'm gonna try and adjust the settings a bit.
More brightness.
I wanted to do that last time, but I forgot.
Gamma is at a hundred.
I'm gonna put it at 150.
Is that overkill?
It seems really crazy.
Like, look at this.
This is 150.
This is this is what We can say 125 just to be, you know, right in between 100 and 150.
Okay, let's let's go with 125.
Seems good to me.
The backlog page is really cool.
Did you make yourself?
Did you use some service?
Well, you could say I made it myself, but regarding tools, I used Claude code for that.
I would say 85% of the code is written by Claude code.
I'm just supervising, you know, making sure everything is as I wanted and there's no security problems with it and stuff like that.
I'm just using the the lowest subscription you can get.
So it's very limited usage with tokens, but you know, good enough for hobby projects like this and just messing around.
I'm not using API.
What I mean is I'm not you know, consuming tokens like that.
I just have like a limit and when that limit is reached doesn't work anymore until in five hours, you know, and then there's like a weekly limited stuff.
I know there's no game audio yet.
I'm not starting yet.
I'm just chilling right now with the music and you know.
Oh, you're talking about the API to query IGDB.
Yes, of course.
Yeah, so all the covers and stuff come from IGDB, the Internet Game Database, which is powered by Twitch apparently.
I didn't know that, but yeah.
Have you heard of Mugenics?
Actually, I haven't.
Tell me more.
Are the backlog entries hard-coded in or is there a DB you put?
So I have a database that's run by Superbase.
It's just SQL pretty much.
It's all hosted on Vercel and I have an admin page set up where I just, you know, I add a game.
I can just search and the search I get is querying IGDB.
So I add the game from there.
I can, you know, choose to have it as played or backlogged, whatever.
Add some notes to it if I want to and add a link to a playlist, you know, stuff like that.
You should consider playing the original Isaac sometimes too.
That game is scuffed as fuck.
You're talking about the browser game, right?
I heard about it.
I don't know if I want to.
I don't feel like playing something that's scuffed.
I like this Isaac.
You got a hundred hours in Flash, Isaac.
Okay.
Well, it must be entertaining enough then.
Are you gonna play Hades?
I did play the first Hades.
One of my favorite games.
It's so good in terms of roguelikes.
I'm looking forward to the second.
I will play it.
Definitely looking forward to that.
I really enjoyed the music and the art and just the gameplay of the first.
Really nice gameplay loop.
Super satisfying.
I love the shield in the first one where you smash into things.
God, that's so satisfying.
But also just the standard sword.
Can you adjust the UI to the edge of the screen on options?
It's the hot offset option.
Hold on.
What are you talking about?
Item descriptions, pop-ups...
Oh, this one?
It's already at max.
Or do you mean this is gonna like center it more?
Set it low?
But isn't that gonna interfere with gameplay area?
In-game I can see the difference.
Okay, I'm gonna play with it in-game, I guess.
It makes more space.
Okay, well, let me put it at lowest and see how it looks.
If I don't like it, I'm gonna put it back.
Let's say that.
Uh, bullet miss a bit.
Wait!
Okay, that's on high.
That's good.
Uh, multi...like multiplayer?
How does that even work?
Wait, streamer mode.
Do you guys know what streamer mode is?
What is that?
No clue?
Huh?
I think it hides multiplayer names.
Oh, okay.
I see.
All of you can see chat now, huh?
Yeah, I was blind, but now I can see, man.
I was at the doctor's, you know, they fixed my eyes.
Up until today, I literally couldn't see.
Music stresses me out good.
I love this music.
It's from inside, but I played it.
A Danish company based in Copenhagen, actually.
For those that don't know, now you do.
The music is reflecting my mental state right now.
I'm feeling a little under the weather.
I have some stuff going on with my throat and my nose.
I mean, obviously, there's some allergies going on, but it's more than that, I feel like.
I just want to play games still.
It's gonna be a more chillax dream.
Now, of course, when I get excited, I can't really contain it, right?
But I'm just telling you now.
Who here is excited for Subnautica 2?
Raise his hand.
I am excited.
I'm also getting super excited about Kingdom Come Deliverance because a lot of people have said that the stuff I like in Red Dead Redemption is like super good in Kingdom Come Deliverance as well.
So, I have so much good stuff to look forward to.
I can't wait to play all of these games.
It's so cute you guys are raising your hands, the little raise handsie mode.
I always loved that when when I had lectures on Zoom during Coronavirus.
You know, someone would ask questions and when people had something to say, they would like had the little hand icon.
I don't know why.
It was always so funny to me.
Yeah, I can't wait for Red Dead 2 as well.
I mean, if it's anything like the first, then I'm sold because I am already super sold on Red Dead 1.
If you couldn't tell already.
For those that have been watching the episodes.
It is just such a vibe, man.
And the crazy part is, I'm not even that big on cowboys.
So, wow, imagine if I was like hyper cowboy fanboy.
Probably would have been my favorite game ever.
You know?
But I'm not.
I mean, cowboys are... they're fine.
I'm just not like, yay, cowboys, you know?
Skinning addiction.
For sure, man.
I love taking off the skin of defenseless animals and seeing their insides.
Come on, guys.
Okay, let's actually do this, huh?
Let's play some Isaac.
I don't know what the plan is today in Isaac.
We're just gonna sort of chill.
Okay.
Who am I?
Oh god, the screen looks so weird with the gamma change.
Wait, win streak is zero?
Oh, I guess I lost the last one.
Hold on, I gotta blow my nose.
Man, I dread the day that I forget to mute myself when I do that.
Because I sound like a wounded animal when I blow my nose.
Especially in local recordings when I make YouTube videos.
Like, I have to press the mute button when I sneeze or whatever, right?
If I forget to do that or I miss the button or something, it's gonna be horrible.
I don't think it's happened yet, but I'm dreading that moment.
None of us would care.
Probably, but it's still something I care about, right?
I don't want to blast your ears with that.
So yeah.
Okay, guys, I will now get into the game and let's do this.
I'll see you on the other side.
What do I want to do?
Do I go for a challenge?
You know what, let's let's start off with something chill.
You know, something nice.
How about a good old Isaac run?
It's been a while.
Let's do an Isaac run.
The burning basement.
And of course, we have the D6, which is insanity.
Oh, hold on.
I need to adjust my desk.
The reason I do this every time, just for those who are curious, I have a big-ass mousepad.
And when I'm playing with the keyboard only, my right arm is leaning on the mousepad and the table.
And the, you know, the transition between those two surfaces is really annoying.
So now I have my arms only on the table because my mousepad is out of the way.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Oh, wait, I see the UI here.
Oh, that's super weird.
Whoa.
Wait a minute.
Do I like that?
Let me think.
I guess it's fine.
Yeah, let's run with that for a bit.
Maybe I'll put it somewhere in between the two extremities and the options.
Good start.
I was about to say, no damage taken yet, but that's not true.
Come here.
I'm gonna wait for this guy to come over here.
Nice.
Not bad.
We're gonna take it slow, this this run here.
This run is a chill run.
We're gonna be looking for tinted rocks and maximizing everything, you know, efficiency.
If I sound a little nasal, it's because I am a little nasal right now, okay?
One and a half d6.
That's interesting.
Maybe I'll take it.
Why not?
You can't have too many d6s, right?
Okay, he's down.
They're gonna charge me with a crime, even though I'm not guilty.
Nice.
Okay, let's see what we get here.
So that one is pause.
Frees all enemies in the current room.
A freeze effect ends early if Isaac fires a tear.
I don't like that.
Knockout drops.
A chance to fire fist shots, which have much stronger knockback and confuse enemies for several seconds on impact.
You know what?
I'll take that.
I'm my d6 for the boss reward then.
Let's say that.
Okay, give me some money then.
Buddy, I keep thinking this is a milk carton.
It's not though.
Fanny pack.
50% chance to drop a pickup when taking damage.
I don't have any money.
Too bad.
I'm actually just gonna do this.
Why?
Because it's fun.
Larry!
Every time I say anything that sounds like Harry, like Larry, I think of that Eric Andre sketch.
Or he's not in buying a car, you know?
I need a car that talks.
So stupid.
Harry!
I'm playing horrible.
Not going well.
Oh, there's healing there.
Nice.
Oh, it's actually a fist that I'm shooting.
I like the old school sound effect.
I'm in a corner here.
Wait, that was kind of cool.
I need more luck, so this can be more effective.
I wonder if there's a cap on how much luck you can have.
Oh, Jesus juice.
I actually kind of like that.
I'm not gonna re-roll it.
It's just too good.
It is actually solid.
Yeah, there it is.
So check it out.
We have two hearts here, which means we can go lose a bit of HP back here and potentially get some items.
God, my character is disgusting looking.
Isaac, what happened to you?
Why do you look like that?
Uh-oh.
Side-step, slightly.
I'm like Spider-Man.
Oh, shit.
Whoa!
I don't like that.
Three black hearts and damage.
I have the occult.
Uh, tears can control... Oh, I don't know if I like that, actually.
Like, it's good, but it's not...
Like, it's fine, right?
I think I want this more.
Especially because I get three black hearts in return, so I'm gonna end up with one red heart, which is not great.
But the extra damage could be fine.
Let's try it.
This may have been a huge mistake.
We will see.
I'm happy with that.
I'm not happy with that!
Oh, you bastard.
Took away my HP.
That's fine.
Rip my blue heart.
Okay, I got one key.
I don't need to exchange anything here.
Oh my god, so many hearts, though.
Wish I could step a little bit.
Okay, moving on.
Cheers.
100% demon mode.
We love seeing that.
Then again, do we want more demon?
We only have one red heart.
I'm not even sure I want to take a deal if I find one.
Unless... unless something I can't think right now.
There is a non-less in there.
Okay, that was actually kind of clean somehow.
I don't know how I did that without taking damage.
Impressive.
Familius orbit around Isaac.
So, see, this I think is a trinket.
So, if I use D6 on it, I can't yet, though.
But if I do, it's not gonna affect it.
Good call.
We can step if we want to.
Cupid's arrow piercing.
I mean, that is good.
But maybe I want to re-roll it.
It's not that good, you know?
I'll come back in the side later.
For now, I'm just gonna move on.
Get some battery on my... on my active.
Okay, so here's the thing.
Let's say I go to the Devil Room and I find Brimstone.
I think in that case, I may actually take it.
Even though I don't have any...
What do you call it?
HP right now, you know?
That would be the one thing I would sacrifice my HP for.
I should probably focus these guys.
Get punched.
Oh my god.
I can't believe I've done this.
Okay.
Oh, come on.
Please be a good heart.
Damn it.
But more hearts like this is good for stepping.
If we end up losing all our black hearts for whatever reason.
Obviously, we don't want that to happen.
You know, it could happen.
Please don't come down here, Spider.
Okay, not too bad.
Our D6 is active.
I really should have gone back there.
Now I'm wasting a charge on it.
Ohoy.
I got two coins.
I am poor as hell.
I didn't think.
Damn it.
See, that was the thing.
Maybe I saved my D6, actually.
You know what?
I'm going to save it for the demon room.
Because we have 100% demon chance.
I'm going to take this item and save the D6 for the demon.
Hoping for a brimstone or something.
This is the plan.
Gimme.
And piercing shots is, you know, good.
But wait, it's different than spectral shots, though.
These ones go through enemies.
These don't go through environments.
There's a difference.
Yeah.
But that's good, too.
A asshole!
Okay.
I can't risk getting hit by that fire.
Here we go!
Dingle time!
This guy's kind of tough.
I really hate when he charges me.
Oh, we got money there, though.
Get punched, nerd.
Oh my god.
Come on.
Kill him.
Nice.
Latch key, assault.
Ooh!
I think I want that, actually.
Let me destroy this.
Okay, not bad.
I'm taking it.
And now we're hoping for the biggest and the baddest.
It really needs to be big before I take it.
This needs to be earth-shatteringly good.
Uh, oh wait, destroy these.
Okay, let me see.
Sulphur.
Branch Brimstone for the current room.
Although it is only three charges.
It's not that bad, but let me reroll.
Spirit of the night.
Grant's flight!
Oh, oh wait, that kills me.
I can't take that.
Death's List, uh, nah.
Killing it, no.
I refuse.
I'm making the adult decision here.
I'm moving on.
We take it slow.
We have a good thing going right now.
Oh yeah, when I go through all three like that.
Uh, these tiers are good, you know?
Piercing tiers.
Like that.
Ah!
I can't afford to lose HP right now.
Man, the punching is really nice.
Gives me space.
Okay, good.
Melted the rock so far.
How did I take damage?
No way.
Well, we're down to 2 HP right now.
It's not good.
Oish.
I don't know why I did it like that.
Okay man, this is actually no problem.
Somehow I'm killing it.
What's all this about?
Wait a second, I smell a secret.
That would have been a good place for it, right?
Look at it.
Maybe here.
Fine.
I didn't want to find a secret anyway.
Keep your secrets then.
Oh man, the piercing tiers, man, are doing work.
Please don't jump at me.
Is that a mega battery?
Or an active?
I'm not going to take it yet, obviously.
Good.
Okay.
I need to find a room with an item in it so I can use my D6 for something.
This room is worse than it looks.
No, it looks worse than it is.
I don't know what I'm trying to say.
It looks more scary than it actually is.
That's what I was trying to say.
Blood donation machine.
I'll blow that up.
Sick.
Why is destruction always so satisfying?
Are we just wired that way?
Man, so many random hearts dropping.
Uh, south.
Oh, no way.
Fucking hell.
Where's the boss at?
Hey, come here.
That is fine.
Lots of batteries in this room.
But I can't get to them.
Actually, I can.
I have nine keys somehow.
Holy shit.
Okay, let's see them.
Oh, that's not very nice.
I don't like that.
We're going to reroll that for sure.
Let me see it again, though.
Spawn ship.
Yeah, I don't care about that.
A new one!
It's an egg.
Mystery egg.
Sacrificial insemination?
I don't like that.
Hatches when Isaac takes damage spawning a permanently charmed monster.
The strength of the monster is increased with each consecutive room cleared without it breaking.
The egg regenerates when entering a new room.
Okay.
Interesting.
That's disgusting.
I could actually get that bomb, but that wouldn't make sense.
Wait, do we have two treasure rooms?
What the?
Okay.
A hollykin baby familiar that fires two tears.
No, I'm going to go reroll that.
That's right.
I'm going to take this.
And some more batteries.
Can I even get to a full charge, though, is the question.
There's a couple of rooms left.
I think I can.
I'm not going to go in there, though.
There's also the big battery.
Let's not forget that.
So that's for the next one.
A battery up there.
No.
I can't believe it.
They're farming tomatoes here.
I knew I sold my soul to the devil when I make that deal, man.
I'm too low HP for this shit.
It was a bad move.
Those three black hearts didn't do nothing for me.
The red hearts would have done exactly as much and even better, because I could have healed it up again, you know?
Okay, let's go in here.
Metal plate.
A soul heart?
Chance to reflect enemy projectiles?
That's a concussive shot.
That's some survival right there.
I like that.
I like it a lot, actually.
And now we're gonna go get more battery, just in case we need to reroll.
There was a mega battery somewhere up here.
Here.
I think this was it.
Yep.
Whoa!
Two charges on it!
Okay, that's sick.
Well, well, well.
I didn't realize that would have two charges.
That's amazing.
I'm gonna go kill the boss now.
It's poop.
Yeah, get punched, nerd.
That was super close.
I punched him back when he was jumping, so he flew super far away from me.
Oh, man.
Oh, he spawned!
No!
Get away from me!
Dude, I'm gonna die here!
Kill him, kill him, kill him.
Thank the lord.
Uh, we can't take it.
We gotta reroll this.
It's just... Oh my god, there's another boss.
You gotta be kidding me.
Oh, man.
Okay, I guess that's fine.
We can take this.
I'm gonna save the other reroll.
Keep going.
I need some HP here, man.
That's what I really need.
Wow.
Oh, right.
Oh my god!
How did I do that?
Wait, how did I die?
I thought I had a full heart.
Shit.
I must have lost HP without noticing, I guess.
I thought I totally could take two hits there.
Weird.
Well, that was a good warm-up game.
How about some random?
Let's do random.
Why is it always Eve?
I swear to god, we get her 80% of the time when we do random.
Am I wrong?
I feel like the whore has become a staple.
It's become a staple of whores.
That was brilliant.
Uh-oh.
Jittery, man.
Jittery!
Okay.
Explosivo.
Chance of fire is sticky too that will grow and explode.
Yeah!
Actually, that's really good.
I dig that a lot.
Oh!
Well, well, well.
Not bad at all.
What do we have here?
The jar.
And what was that one?
Coins and spawns more coins when taking damage.
This is a good investment early on.
The earlier you get this, the better, right?
So this one... not really that cool.
We can also re-roll if we need to.
Let's see what we got here.
We don't know.
I'm not gonna go in there.
I'm too scared.
We're gonna step!
Yes, dude!
It's a stepping time!
Look!
Finally, the stars are aligning for the step.
Insanity.
Wait, did I take a full heart of damage there?
I thought it was half a heart of damage when you step on that.
What the hell?
Okay, well.
The scary thing is though, if I step too much, I'm gonna be fighting an angel with one HP.
Which is kinda, you know...
Not very good.
But I guess I'll have a lot of HP or damage at that point.
So we have 2.62 damage now.
And I had 5 point something before.
Let me see now.
3.23, so 5.86.
Go back again.
Kinda tedious to go back and forth, but...
I need to do it.
I need to.
Sick!
I mean, this is a great start!
No matter what happens, this is a great first floor.
Just in terms of items we find and all that.
I could've sworn this place took half a heart and then later on it was one heart.
You feel blessed?
We're gonna go all the way.
Or at least as far as we can.
If we die to the angel, fine.
It is what it is.
Maybe I'll try and bomb the angel when it spawns.
I think I also have bombs on my tears.
Huh.
I'm gonna use that later for healing.
When we're gonna fight the angel.
That's actually pretty good.
Hopefully I'll get even more hearts.
Woah!
Sick!
Nice.
This item is kinda fun.
A little unpredictable, but fun.
It does require you to have some knowledge about the game.
You know, like...
The text that comes up, you need to understand what it does.
Oh shhh...
Noooooo!
Fuck that, man.
Yes!
No!
God damn it...
Dude, when I saw those bombs spawn and I saw the way they were aligned.
I knew I was gonna die.
Like, I saw it before it happened.
I just knew it.
Like of course I tried to dodge it, but I just knew I was gonna die.
I knew it.
What is this?
Scatter bombs.
Sure.
I'm not excited about these items.
Like, at all.
Maybe I'll try and go fast.
Semi-speedrun, perhaps.
Nah.
Ah, maybe.
We'll see.
Depends what items I'm gonna get.
Come here, you.
Jumping jack.
Jump towards me, please.
Okay, that took a while.
We got the boss here.
We could go fast.
Let's do it.
Larry!
I don't trust like that.
Wait, if we're speedrunning, let me do this.
Actually sick.
I'm not gonna waste another bomb, though.
Ooh, nice.
I like that one.
Nothing else I wanna grab from here, I think.
Go, speed.
I still can't die or accept the way I died on that last run.
That was atrocious.
What a shame.
That was such a promising start.
It could have been so much fun, you know?
The ultimate step.
Fuck off.
Took my soul heart there.
Kinda wanna grab these pills.
Yeah.
I'm excited for pills.
Oh my god.
Terrible pills.
Well, that's the way she blows.
It is RNG.
There we go.
Some good luck.
Uh oh, uh oh.
Actually, I don't mind this.
This is nice.
Okay.
That's too bad.
I did in fact mind it.
I like the music when I was sped up, actually.
Oh, let's not forget, we have more damage now.
Oh, shit.
Uh oh.
I'm gonna go get that healing.
Okay.
That's not where the boss is.
Man, we're not fast enough.
We gotta be faster.
Okay, this is huge.
Let's see what we got here.
I don't know what that item is.
I think I've seen it before.
Uh, eyesore.
Each tier has a chance to fire one of the three additional shots.
Uh... Doesn't seem that great.
Oh, I hate the way my character looks.
Ew.
Disgusting.
Yep.
We're going full pill.
That was a bad decision.
It happens.
I can't believe I went every direction except the one frickin' place where the boss was.
We have to be behind now.
Wait, didn't this guy used to shoot lasers?
The little guy?
Or are you thinking of another one?
There's someone else who has, like, a little follower.
Oh, okay.
Torn photo.
Not great.
Not bad, either.
Oh, yes, I like these places.
This is good.
There's the other guy.
Someone else is hiding in the water, I think.
Or he died?
He died, okay.
No way.
Dude, my shot speed is off the charts for some reason.
Why is that?
Let me see something.
I guess the torn photo.
I mean, it is almost one tier, right?
Which is kind of a lot.
Smartfly.
Locks enemy shots, and when I take damage, it chases and damages them.
I'll take it.
God damn it, man.
Open.
Faster.
I'm gonna die here.
Maybe.
Dying that one time, though, is painful.
Yeah, we're at 1 HP now, man.
It's not looking good.
I don't have any healing lying around.
Oh, no.
I gotta stay at range here.
If we can buy something for $3?
No, we don't have enough.
I can blow this guy up, though.
No.
I was gonna get that heart.
God damn it.
Dude, I am just not doing well.
I can't seem to do anything today.
Just dying to random shit.
Eden.
Oh, I haven't had that guy in a while.
That's the guy with randomized items, right?
Bop's rotten head.
That's Isaac threw a poison bomb.
Anti-gravity.
Tears will hover in place while pressing attack button.
Releasing attack button will shoot all hovering tears.
Okay.
That's kinda cool, I guess.
Yeah.
I can't charge it up before I go in, though, right?
And then, nah, okay.
That would be too good to be true.
Suck on that.
No way I thread the needle like that.
Like, what the hell?
Huh.
Chance to fire tooth shots to deal... I wonder if this works while I'm charging, or if it's...
Wow, that chance is atrocious.
What a shit item.
Okay, you're dead.
It's like me stopping bullets in midair and shooting them back at the enemy.
It's kinda dope, actually.
Ooh!
Oh my god.
Oh my god, we need money.
Please, I need money.
I need it real bad.
Especially with my current health setup.
This is what's gonna save this run.
Yep.
Oh my god.
It's kinda awkward to shoot like this, though, with the delay on it, you know?
But it's not that bad.
Wait,
I can use this almost like a creep, you know?
Enemies follow me and walk into my shots.
That's one way to utilize that.
It's a Duke of Flies.
Wow.
Nice.
That's huge.
I really needed that.
A wash battery.
Increased chance of little batteries spawning.
Chance to replace a room reward with a little battery.
Hey!
Is that better than this, though?
I think this is better for my current item, because it only has two charges, right?
Which is kinda nuts.
Shit.
No secret there.
Man, I wanna buy this so bad.
Why you gotta give me this in the beginning of the game?
What a shame that is.
Breaks my heart.
Okay.
It's not the end of the world.
Curse of the Unknown.
I don't know how much HP I have.
Walk into my... Yeah, come here.
The tank is kinda good.
Hey, check this out.
Oh, I don't have any battery.
I'm actually gonna wait, then.
Nice.
Alright.
Let's do it here.
Beautiful.
Wait, you can actually do something like this.
I had them shoot in both directions.
Hey, check this out.
That's kinda cool.
Not super useful, but, you know.
It's cool.
I need keys, so I'm actually gonna do this.
Amazing!
What do we got here?
What is... It's a new one!
Fortune cookie!
Wait.
Oh, is it gonna be the mobile version of that machine?
A chance to drop a soul heart, card, rune, or trinket.
It displays a random fortune if no item drops.
Wait a minute, so is that what that other machine does?
Wait.
Fortune machine.
We're gonna note that down.
This is actually kinda big.
Let's see here.
Fortune machine can spawn...
What was it?
Soul heart, card, rune, or trinket.
That actually tracks with my experience, too.
Sick.
Ah, fuck you then.
I'm actually gonna come back for this bomb later.
I wanna go around collecting some fortunes.
And I do want that key.
Can I not get that key?
Maybe if I go north immediately.
There we go.
Ah, then again.
Nah, I'm gonna keep it for now.
Dude, I'm actually kinda digging this setup here.
Wait, something else I noticed.
If I put them stationary like this and then I move while shooting...
No, wait, how does that work?
So if I move by pulling them down and then...
Then they... Ah, I see.
So that momentum is saved, I guess.
It's delayed.
You know what I mean?
If I move while doing this, they have, like, safe momentum in diagonal directions.
That's kinda cool.
Get a baby pet.
Nah.
Thank you.
Oh, is that the sprinkler?
Fuck off with that.
Boo!
I don't even wanna touch that.
Yikes.
That's what I'm talking about.
Okay.
Getting lots of bombs.
We'll all die one day.
It's kinda sad, isn't it?
I wanna live forever.
I wanna see all the games in the future.
I'm gonna miss all the games in 21.50.
Imagine the games they have at that point, man.
Holy shit.
I'm not gonna be there to see it.
So sad.
Imagine Binding of Isaac in 21.50.
You think anyone's still gonna be playing this game in 21.50?
Maybe.
Okay.
You're annoying me.
Not getting lucky with that thing.
I'm actually gonna get in here.
Too bad, no secret discovered.
Aha!
Dude, nice.
Underwear.
Why not?
Wasted all my flies there.
Shit.
That just damaged me, I think.
That was a damage.
Let's go heal up.
If it actually damaged my health.
Maybe damaged my blue health.
Not sure.
Yeah, it did.
Okay.
Now, we gotta shop in eight coins.
One key only, though.
I don't know if I should use the key on that.
That is a very bare-boned shop.
What is this?
There's nothing in here.
Oh my god.
What a waste.
I'm gonna go get my bomb now.
I've had enough of the fortune cookie.
The bomb is goaded.
It is so good for my damage right now.
Especially with the AAA battery.
Helps a lot.
Means I can use it once per room, pretty much.
No.
God dammit.
Okay.
I can also use this to look for secrets here.
Then again, I have five bombs.
Let me actually do this.
Okay.
For some reason, I was very convinced.
That we had a secret right there.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
The bomb is goaded.
Tears and shot speed.
Yes, sir.
Shovel?
Nah.
Generates a trail of damage and creep.
You know, I think I'm gonna save for angels.
That's right.
I think we're going all angels.
Yep.
This is gonna be an angel run.
Okay, look at all the blue hearts.
Ah, you gotta be fucking with me.
Jesus, what a shit room that was.
I can't believe it.
Just take all my HP, will you?
Just kill me in this room right now.
End the run right now, man.
I don't like the stacking of charges on my shots.
It's really annoying.
Insane.
Can't even get in there.
Whew.
I was so happy exactly 15 seconds ago and now it's all turned to shit.
You like bombs so much.
Please die.
Thank you.
Ha ha ha ha.
What is this?
Quint's first five enemies killed will spawn a random friendly baby.
Familiar spawn by this effect are stationary and last only for the current room.
Sure.
Why not?
I need you to follow me.
Come here.
Oh yeah, look at them.
They're spawning.
It's working.
There's still a treasure room.
I gotta find a key here.
Okay, these assholes right there.
Let's go over here.
There has to be a key somewhere.
Oish.
Nothing.
Wait, I have a little brimstone right now.
But they're stationary.
We got a key.
But we're also dying.
So it's not really that great.
God damn it!
I can't dodge anything today, dude.
I almost went in there.
Mmm, up here.
Man, if only I had that converter, it would've changed everything.
Ugh!
What a shit item.
All that work for nothing.
Made me lose all my HP as well.
Whoops.
Thanks.
I guess.
Okay, we're gonna bomb this guy.
Polycephalus.
You gotta be kidding me!
It didn't hit him?
Why not?
Okay.
No way.
Are we done?
Okay.
Okay, I needed that one badly.
Whew.
This run is a disaster.
I don't think there's any way we can win with this.
Oh, no.
Okay,
I frickin' hate this item right now.
I just wanna shoot normal tears.
Can I please?
Fucking gimmick.
That should work.
Hairpin?
Fully charges Isaac's active item when entering a new boss room.
Very unexciting.
I also have a massive damage problem right now.
Like, I just don't do any damage.
Except for when I have a bomb.
Yeah!
Okay, I think we may be back.
If we can find some damage now, we're golden.
Three hearts is good.
Bro, I'm so confused by all the crap that's spawning on my screen.
That item that's doing this is making me think there's enemies everywhere.
Nice tinted rock there.
Oh, wait, you're not dead.
The good news is, though, no more blue hearts.
We got red hearts.
I actually can't...
Uh...
Like, I hate blue hearts.
They're just... fucking terrible, man.
Uh, what's this?
Blasting cap?
Boom!
Of course, they still managed to hit me.
Um, what is the plan?
Uh, go up here first.
I love the bomb, man.
It is carrying this run.
Because my tier situation is garbage.
The bomb and the AAA battery are just carrying this right now.
What's that?
A little unicorn...
Fucking actives!
I don't want it!
Give me some good items, please.
I'll take the blue heart, I guess.
Can't really afford anything else.
No, no, no.
Absolutely not.
Wait, how did I not kill him?
Look at that little angel buddy spawn.
Stop shooting, guys.
I think I just want to move on.
So, find the boss.
Could heal with that.
Yo, this is actually kind of sick.
But to get over there...
Oh, cool.
Dope!
There's got to be something here.
I got you baited by that.
What about here?
No?
Okay.
I'll take it.
So, this has to be the boss room.
Mmm, the emperor.
Oh, the emperor.
Oh, the teleport.
I mean, I could do that, I guess.
This room is made of nightmares for me.
It's like, tailored to fuck me, you know?
What is that?
A lucky toe!
Chance to add an additional pickup.
Oh, no, it's a trinket, right?
I need the battery.
Like, this is my damage.
I need my damage.
Chup!
Yeah, there we go.
Good hit.
See, that's what I'm talking about.
And more health?
Okay, but what about the damage situation?
The damage situation is the problem right now.
If I can't find reliable ways of doing damage, then this run is over, right?
Like, the health is good.
We're good on health.
Totally happy with that right now.
You
know, saving up these is actually good for walking and having them rock into it.
I mean, I can't even speak English here.
Oh, I shouldn't have released them.
Oi!
No!
Uh-oh.
Oh, my God!
Crazy.
Man.
Just kill him!
Man, I'm getting some difficult rooms today, man.
Some of these rooms have been killer.
Wait, how did you spawn?
Ah, I see.
Okay.
I think next floor is mom.
I'm gonna leave a trail here.
And then walk into it.
Yeah, that's good.
Maybe that should be the strategy, you know?
Like, every time.
Let's go.
Adversary.
I'm gonna leave a trail.
I'm scared of him doing the laser.
Yeah, there it is.
Okay, I mean, more spiders is good, because that spawns more stuff for me.
More minions.
Okay.
Not too shabby.
That went pretty well.
Shot speeds, uh, increases chance of planetariums.
I mean, I would love to see more planetariums.
Another boss.
Oh, actually.
Ah, good.
Oh, it is mom?
Okay.
I thought it was next floor.
Nice.
Good hit, good hit.
I think I'm just gonna walk in a circle here and leave trails.
Okay, not that big of a circle.
Smaller circle.
Oh my god, come on.
Okay.
Yes, yes.
Not bad.
Bomb it.
Ah, too late.
No, no way.
Little fucking flies are killing me.
Focus, focus.
Oh, no.
God damn it, man.
I can't play this game today, dude.
I can't win.
To be fair, though, like, that starting setup on Eden was brutal.
What a shit start.
Samson.
What is his deal anyway?
What was his deal?
Something about...
I mean, he has pretty good damage, I guess.
Ah, normal attack.
Whoo!
Thank god.
Oh, that's good.
Nails.
That's what I want to see.
Very huge.
Good start.
Love
it.
Oh.
And a lock up as well.
Now, that's a fantastic start.
He's also have increased knockback.
For some reason, I thought they would have piercing, but...
Much better.
Okay, nothing there.
I don't know what this guy's deal is, actually.
Ah, yeah.
Why not?
And three hearts as well?
This character's solid.
Man, what a tease of a room.
Gotta find a bomb.
Or two.
Ooh, we could also go to the library.
Wait a minute.
Maybe we do that first.
No, I can't find anything there.
There's no way there's a bomb in here, though, huh?
Book of Belial?
Actually sick?
That's a good amount of damage?
Unfortunately, no bomb.
That's crazy.
We're gonna slap this boss now.
Look at his damage now.
It's gonna be crazy.
Demon mode engage.
Yeah, that damage is pretty damn good, and this is just a normal attack.
Not bad.
Still no bombs.
Maybe I can get bombs from this.
Come on, please.
Okay.
What a tease, though.
There was a tinted rock and a black heart.
But this is a great start.
I'm not gonna complain about that.
That is fantastic.
All things considered, I'm golden.
Oh, that felt amazing.
I don't know why I went in here.
That was a waste.
Mistake.
Nope, nope, nope.
Fuck off.
I don't know if I should take that yet, actually.
Because I'm thinking of stepping.
So maybe I'll take that after I step.
Depends how much HP we find.
Red hearts, I mean.
Doubles the keys.
I'm gonna hold on to that for a bit.
Any tinted rocks?
No.
But aren't these rocks kind of huge?
These rocks are massive.
Careful of the creep.
Ah, we're chilling.
No problem.
Man, all the health in the world.
We got health and damage.
It can't be better than this.
This is great.
Momma's in here too.
Okay, come on.
There we go.
Two spooky tiers and shot speed.
Applies fear to enemies in close range.
Committed to fire spectral tiers and guppies.
No, absolutely not.
I think I want to take this.
Yeah.
That's a good one.
Now that I have good damage, more tiers is gonna be massive for me, you know?
I could maybe go step a little bit.
Depends what we're gonna find.
I think I should explore everything.
I haven't found treasure room either, right?
So, we're gonna save that heart.
Batteries.
Okay, let's see here.
What is that one?
Bursting sack.
Many spider enemies become less dangerous.
I love that!
Fuck the spiders, man.
This is gonna make everything so much better.
Yes.
Huge fan of that item.
And now I think we're just gonna grab the heart and get out.
Maybe we go into the curse room.
This better be a good one.
Is this the best one of all time?
What the fuck?
Holy!
Like, this is pot raising.
That's what it is.
We're leaving.
I pretty much made that Devil Deal 3, if you think about it.
You know what's funny?
When I had those shitty runs before?
Where I couldn't figure out how to dodge shit and I got bad items and all that.
I was paying more attention to how sick I was, you know?
And I was like, oh, I feel terrible.
Now that things are going well, it's like I'm forgetting that I'm feeling down, you know?
It's just powering me.
Games can have that effect on you.
They can heal you.
I had that same experience with certain movies in the past where I was really sick, you know?
To the point where even the idea of watching a movie was like, oh, I don't know if I can do that.
You know, I just want to lie in my bed and cry.
But then I put on a movie and it was so good.
A Fight Club.
And I hadn't seen it before at the time.
And I was just so engrossed that I forgot I was sick.
I felt healthy while watching it.
And then when the movie was over, I felt like shit again.
Okay, slowly.
Oh, you bastard, coming in from the side down there.
I don't like when you do that.
Can you stop doing that?
Come up here.
No problem.
Kidney Bean.
Oh, guys, this is even more goated than Belial.
I'm not kidding.
We're going to kill each other now.
Maybe these guys are the worst example, but this thing is insane.
It's so unassuming, but it's actually amazing.
And the best part, it only has one charge and it recharges.
Nice.
I could go in there, but not yet.
It's the ultimate oh shit button.
Look at that.
This room became trivial when I pressed spacebar.
It's so good.
Oh, I love this so much.
The Bean.
Kill each other.
Get away from me.
Ah, I did it too early.
Go kill him.
Oi, I got a little daisy.
What if I charm this guy?
Oh, okay.
Well, boss is here.
I think I'm just going to go in.
Mega fatty.
Not bad.
This guy is actually kind of easy.
One of the easier bosses for sure.
It's just back and forth.
No problem.
Damage and luck.
Love it.
Great.
Scott.
I'm not done here.
What do I want?
I got a bunch of bombs.
Amazing.
You know what?
I think I'm going to take my money and leave with a win when it comes to those pills right now.
Why did I just do that?
Dude, I was in auto mode right now.
I was in autopilot.
I can't even explain why I just did that.
That made no sense at all.
Maybe I'll buy this.
No, I can't afford it.
Go sell.
I was in... I'm making britches mode right now, so I make britches.
Okay, we can afford the blue heart now.
But I think I want to save for 15 coins for the next shop.
If you look for secrets, I have four bombs.
All right, go step.
You know what?
Let's go step.
All right, I guess this is not stepping.
This is the other thing.
School bag!
Yo!
We can go grab the other item.
Not bad.
The best of both worlds now.
Both these items are good, you know?
I would say the bean is better than this book.
But this book, I think, is better late game.
But hold on, does that scale or how does that work?
Damage up for the current room.
Maybe it scales, you know, depending on how much damage you have.
If it's like a percentage increase, then I would say it's better late game.
Actually, both are pretty good.
All right, we're leaving.
The fact that I got pretty fly and health up is kind of massive.
That's why I'm not taking any more pills, because I already got so lucky.
It can only go downhill from now, you know what I mean?
And I think that's the right decision.
Oh, you bastards.
These guys don't really care about being torn for some reason.
They're just happy to be existing, you know?
Go off and do great things.
No, thanks.
Yeah, no, thanks.
Become my friend.
Ah, I really should be at a distance here.
Like, just stay at range.
There's no reason to get in there.
No reason to be cute.
And I can't hit anything.
It's actually impressive.
Just out of range.
Nice!
Of course we take that.
That's the good thing about identifying good pills, you know?
You know when they appear again.
Kill him!
Come on!
Ah!
Fine.
Get him!
Wait, I don't think these guys are actually dealing damage.
They would have killed him by now.
Yeah, he wasn't even damaged.
He's not gonna eat himself?
Come here, come here!
Okay, what's the status?
No treasure room, no shop, no nothing.
I think it's fine, we can actually go in here.
Chat?
Who the hell is that?
Sounds awesome!
Ah, you bastard.
Friendly fire, man, you were on my side.
Little chat has appeared!
Did that say Scotch?
Little chat gives kisses?
What?
Familia that drops a half red heart every three... Whoa!
That's cool!
I like that.
That's really good for me right now as well, because of all the red hearts I have.
Go kill him!
That's it.
Now you die.
Ah, fourteen coins is what I have.
Let's take a look.
BFF, doubles the damage of familiars.
That's gotta be good for my flies.
I'm gonna blow this up.
Richness!
Should I buy that health?
Probably.
My flies are gonna do so much damage.
This run is fun, man.
I'm having a blast in this one.
And I love farting on people.
This item is just too fun.
Yeah, go charge your friend!
You know that scene from...
Liar Liar with Jim Carrey when he's in the elevator and he farts and he goes...
It was me!
That's what I feel like every time I fart in these rooms, you know?
At least that's what I imagine.
And it makes me laugh.
Shit.
I could head down into that room.
Let's do it, actually.
I feel like I have good experience with those rooms.
Curse rooms.
Spider enemies are not dangerous.
Oi!
Mom!
Mom is here.
Gotta be careful.
Are we done?
We're not done.
Mom?
Oh, it's the spiders!
Right, okay.
Sulfur...
Oh, I mean...
Following Familia that generates...
Let's not forget that we do more damage with Familiars now.
This one is good, though.
Since I can have two of these items, I could actually go for Sulfur.
I mean, that is massive.
If we save that for every boss room, right, that's pretty much, like, amazing.
And if we use Belial with that... Ooh, that could be good, right?
I'm taking this.
Yeah, I like that combo a lot.
I'm gonna save the remaining HP.
Maybe I grab this?
No, no, no.
This is fine.
I'm happy.
I'm very happy.
I don't wanna overdo it.
We have only four hearts right now.
Okay.
Wait, we have 12.7 damage?
Also, we're red.
Is that the mechanic here?
I think that was it.
Like, you wanna be blood-drunk, right?
Oh, shit.
Get away from me.
But now I'm sad I don't have the fart capabilities.
Yeah, the damage is very good right now.
Get blown up, nerd.
Nine coins.
I could go gamble.
Why not, actually?
We can blow some stuff up in there.
I can donate half a heart.
Blow that up.
Sick.
This thing, we're gonna blow up as well.
And this thing.
Destruction is beautiful.
This is the most comfortable cleanup of this room I've ever done.
Wow.
Oh, no.
It had to ruin it, huh?
It had to ruin it.
Oi!
A door has opened in the distance.
Somewhere far off.
Nobody knows where.
But it's there.
And boy, is it open.
I can't wait to find that room.
Bumbo!
Familiar that wanders around consuming coin pickups from the ground.
Levels up as it consumes coins.
Gaining new abilities that can damage enemies and spawn items.
Hey!
I mean, he's gonna do more damage as well because I have that item, right?
The one item.
Okay, we're done here.
Solid floor.
I do have 17 coins.
Maybe let me check out the shop once more.
I bought everything.
I can't believe it.
We even killed the boss.
This is nice.
We just move on.
16 keys.
16 times the unlocking.
Oh, no.
Curse of the Labyrinth.
Oh, wait.
It's not the last one, though.
This is fine.
I can really use my fart mechanism.
Oh, shit.
What is this?
This room is fucking crazy!
Wow!
What if I didn't have the fear effect?
I would be toast!
That has to be one of the craziest rooms I've ever seen in this game.
Wow!
What a chest.
Jackpot right there.
I don't trust myself.
Not bad.
I thought maybe if I pre-charged it from this room to the next, I could keep my brimstone.
Just for one shot.
Doesn't work like that.
Oh, my God.
Ah, bro.
This room is going to kill me.
I just want to get to the boss.
Man, I missed my fart.
I actually think I made a mistake picking up.
I should have kept the fart.
Mom's purse allows two trinkets.
Wow!
So backpack and purse.
Why not?
Oh!
Where's an increase to all stats when health...
Yeah, I mean, I pretty much have that at full charge all the time anyway.
That's lovely.
Let me take that.
I saved these actors for a rainy day.
Yeah, here we go.
The fart here would be crazy.
Ah, went okay.
Not that guy, it's the...
Yeah, come on.
The other guy's down here.
Whoo!
The game is testing me, man.
Not easy.
What a weird layout for a floor.
Look at that.
Ooh, well, let's see here then.
Yeah, you best believe I take that.
Wonderful.
Good stuff.
Now this one...
Wait, I wonder if I can...
I mean, I have 16 keys.
Who cares?
Wow.
So wait.
If I hold this button, I job everything.
Okay.
Just had to check.
But there was a way to switch the order of...
Nah.
I think at least there was.
Maybe it doesn't matter what trinkets.
Oh!
Oh,
just kill him.
Oh man.
This is why I need a lot of HP, guys.
Oh, close one.
No tinted rocks anywhere?
Okay, we can get some more blue hearts here, maybe.
Too bad.
Oh man, this room is gonna be problematic, I think.
The fear helps a lot against those.
Because they turn around and then you can shoot them.
Turn around!
Hot bombs!
Place bombs, deal contact damage.
I think spawn explosions leave behind fires that can damage enemies.
Grants immunity to damage from stationary.
I like it.
And look, I shine brightly now, too.
What a nice side effect.
Wow, I actually dodged that.
I'm still gonna open it.
So it is possible to dodge that.
Gotta be fast.
Oh, this room is crazy.
When they reach me over here, I'm gonna be in trouble.
Gotta kill them fast.
Okay, not bad.
Oh wait, there's more.
Wow.
Homing tears.
I'm going.
Get away from me.
Not bad, not bad.
And so, that's very underwhelming.
But I take this.
Oh wait, there's more.
Aha!
Well, now I really should have saved my fucking items, huh?
My access would have been great here.
Ah, this one should be easy.
We got everything going for us here.
Good.
Good dodge.
Come on, mom, I'm waiting for your foot.
Good amount of damage there.
That was clean.
That was super clean.
Very nice.
Polaroid.
Okay.
Not bad.
I think this is a slam dunk.
The question is though, do we go to hell or do we go to heaven?
Kind of want to go to heaven.
Because we can go inside a box, right?
And I want to do that.
Oh god.
You guys are bloody as hell.
I take that.
Oh god, oh god.
Wow.
Dude, this room is crazy.
Holy shitballs.
At least they get feared.
This is saving me right now.
Wow.
Somehow I nailed that.
I can't explain how.
Dude, this room is...
I feel like the game is getting harder faster than I'm getting better.
You know what I mean?
And I...
It's crazy, like some of these rooms are just...
It's too much for me, you know?
There's too much.
I can't not take damage.
Grinch.
Take care of the little guys first.
Please let us find the boss fast.
There's no shops here anyway.
I mean, there's a treasure room, I guess.
Is there actually...
Is there a treasure room in the room?
Or uterus, whatever you want to call it.
I'm not even sure what the difference is between those two.
I'm taking a lot of damage here.
Wait, what is happening?
Wow.
Well, that was rough.
That was a rough room.
I think we're done.
I think it's the end of the run.
What's that?
Crosses, tears, pulse and size.
Actually, why not?
We're just gonna be sitting back here.
And wait.
Maybe we're sitting here.
I need healing.
And I need it now.
I can't risk it.
Okay, that's good.
At least we don't die to one hit now.
Oh, I need to let that guy pick up coins.
Fuck!
I thought I hit the brimstone!
Total fuck up there.
Yeah.
Man, this game is too fucking hard for me.
I don't know what to say.
I can't win anymore.
The game is getting harder than I'm getting better.
Yeah!
Fuck you!
Teasing me like that.
Okay.
Just fucking kill me, dude.
This room already...
Nah, no way.
Jesus.
Kill me.
Take me out of my misery.
Oh my God.
What a start to that one.
Let's do challenges.
Let's try... what sounds fun?
I really want to unlock eight, though, so I can keep going, you know?
Let's do Suicide King.
What is that?
It's fucking Lazarus!
What the fuck is that?
Huh?
Wait, what?
It comes back at me.
Is that why it's called Suicide King?
I mean, as long as I hit him like that, this is actually not bad.
Look at that damage, though.
Hello.
I dig it.
Can we blow this up?
Oh shit.
Yeah, we can.
Huge.
All right, I'm digging this challenge.
I was like, Lazarus, I don't know about that, but then, you know...
Let's see what we get here.
Boink!
Is that snot?
No, it's poison, okay.
I don't think that's going to be very good on me.
Oh wait, I should be looking for secrets.
Not there, though, because there's rocks.
Uh...
Yeah!
If I miss with that, you know, it's bad.
There we go.
Wait, I just lost luck?
I'm at minus three luck.
Okay, well, sure.
Oi!
Dude!
What?
I thought I would shoot it over the fucking mushroom.
Ah!
Aha!
Okay, it's a little difficult.
You gotta get some practice with this, for sure.
Gotta have good aim.
Oh, look at this.
Nice!
Huge.
We're gonna look for more secrets as well.
I keep thinking it's gonna go over the rocks, but it's not how that works.
But see, now it goes over the rocks.
It's confusing.
If you're too close, though, it's not gonna go over.
Aight!
Bullshit.
Let's go.
I think bosses are gonna be super easy as this character.
Just because of the damage we do here.
Like, look at that.
That's crazy.
I should be more careful, though.
Like, I'm a little too eager to blow myself up.
I will admit that.
Look for more secrets.
Oi!
Don't blow yourself up.
You gotta walk while shooting.
That's the guaranteed way to make sure you don't get hit by your own shot.
Nice.
Okay, I don't know what this is.
But...
Ooh, the coupon.
I'm going pills, though.
That's actually kind of bad for me.
With this setup.
But now I know what that pill looks like.
I will never pick that up again, though.
Ahh!
Fuck you.
I hate it.
I'm actually gonna go in here.
I feel like we have HP to spare, you know?
Oh, my God.
Ahh!
Oh!
Okay.
Please die, thank you.
Whoo!
Man.
That shit is fucked up.
I need more range.
That's what I need.
Money!
We go back to the shop, baby.
That's huge.
Ahh!
This one.
Fuck!
Come on.
Man!
That's so sad.
Oh, wait, we have this?
Oh, I forgot.
Yo.
Actually insane.
We're gonna get it.
What is it?
Bloody recharge.
It's not an active.
Grants one bar of charge to the active item for every 15 kills.
That's a pretty solid item, especially because it's free.
We're gonna grab the other battery.
And we're gonna move on.
Ah, wait, should I grab the...
There was still a bag I could pick up, right?
Just one more thing.
Yes, we'll take it.
Okay.
A little is still something.
Now we grab the last battery.
Actually, there's even more batteries if I wanted.
How am I actually gonna do this?
So...
Yeah, that works.
Still getting money.
I should destroy these pots.
Definitely difficult to get used to here.
Yeah, I'm good now.
I'm good.
Maybe this one.
Can there be a secret room in the boss room?
I wonder.
I don't think I've ever seen that.
I think that's one, you know, limitation we can wrap our heads around.
And say it definitely cannot be next to that room, you know?
Oh, God.
Suck on that.
For you.
Nice.
Man, this challenge is actually super fun.
Just...
It's glass cannon style, you know?
It's scary, but it's like fun.
High reward, high danger.
Or risk.
And then sometimes you have that happen.
Get some battery there just because we killed enemies.
Lucky penny.
Should offset some of the bad luck we have.
I think we go.
We got coupon ready.
Oh, crap.
Oh, no.
Good night.
Speed and shot speed.
I think shot speed is good.
And speed, of course, is really good.
Unfortunately, no devil deal.
Oh, my God.
That one was right on my ass.
Good thing we have healing.
Let's find a shop and start using this coupon, huh?
Hey.
Oh, man.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, my God.
Look at this set up here.
Nice.
There it is.
OK, so according to...
We're going to get soul, heart, card, rune or trinket here.
So I would say worthwhile investment.
But before we do.
Get in here and make things free.
So I think what I'm going to do is buy some of the cheap stuff first.
Wait, upon purchasing a shop item, a new item immediately takes its place.
I should...
Hold on.
So that was technically not a purchase.
So if I do this...
OK, I see.
Oh, well.
Whoa.
More money.
Very good.
There's also a pill here.
Unidentified.
Why not?
Oh, hell.
Oh, well.
Sick.
Gobby's collar.
Hey, that's sick.
Incredible room.
Holy.
X2 on revive now.
Let's try and look for more secrets.
Oh, wow.
Look, we're shooting coins.
Ultra Greed would approve of this.
OK, let's go back in here now.
Oh, wait.
Show me the good stuff.
Ah, there we go.
Wow.
What's that?
Mom's pearl.
Oh, it's a trinket.
Increased chance of finding...
I mean, OK.
All right.
These machines are kind of goaded.
We're also going to blow it up at the end.
One last.
That was totally worth.
Time to get out.
I don't think I forgot anything on this floor.
A lot of caves.
Yes, we'll look for those.
Definitely destroying these.
Getting good at aiming this.
Oh, I knew that wasn't bad.
I can't even speak.
We go west.
Oh, those are my flies.
Scared me a little bit.
I wonder.
Oh, I'm not going to...
No, I'm not going to gamble.
I'm just going to use a normal bomb for this one.
I don't trust like that.
I could actually reach that too in there.
Minus one range.
Like here.
It's just one coin, but you know.
I want to use my...
I don't want to say condom, but coupon is what it's called.
I want to use that.
Get some use out of it here.
There's probably an item called a condom in this game.
It wouldn't surprise me at all.
And then the description for the item would be because it's fitting in the game.
It would be too bad it wasn't used.
You know, just to rub it in even more.
Now this item right here.
Come on, come on, baby.
Give me a seven.
Ah, fuck.
Too bad.
But...
Okay, come on, come on, come on, baby.
Ah, fuck.
We need more.
Oh, wait, you want bombs?
Maybe you'll give me money?
Thanks.
More money?
Get more money.
Yeah, yeah.
Bro, dude.
I feel like my lock stat is inversely proportional with how good the items are that I'm getting.
That was my last.
But I can buy the battery.
What?
Oh, it's the pill.
Oh!
This room is just a cruel joke.
I'm being messed with.
No way, man.
Okay, we can buy another battery.
Let's try again.
Come on.
Yes!
Treasure map, fully visible map.
That's insane.
Reveals the layout of rooms on the map, so is this gonna be for every floor?
That's...
just unheard of.
I don't think it's gonna reveal secrets, though.
That's a bummer.
Ah, that was bad.
Nah, I think I want this instead.
Boss is here.
Ooh, it's gonna be really nice against this guy to have the bomb attack.
Maybe I take it back.
Fuck me, man.
Suicide king indeed.
I'm out here killing myself.
Yes!
Man, the bar of soap, though, is...
really underwhelming, isn't it?
Fuck, I don't have battery, man.
Aww.
I'll take this, though.
That's fine.
Too bad.
Oh, wait, it's gonna stay open, right?
Hold on a minute.
Ooh.
Ah, but do I want Belial?
I think I do, just to get one out of three on books.
Yeah, actually.
Yeah.
That's smart.
More money.
And we got charged now.
All right, let's go back.
There's nothing else in the shop that I want.
We bought everything.
Yeah!
And then we take this again.
Not bad!
I like that play.
I think that was good.
I don't want to call it too early, but I think we got this challenge in the bag.
We got two lives, man.
It's looking good, right?
Okay.
What?
Oh.
Wait, I can just enter?
Why?
Huh?
Wait, what just happened?
How was I able to exit?
I don't understand what just occurred.
Do I have some item that does that?
None of these.
Oh!
That's where...
That's where I get that from.
Ah!
I can't believe I never looked at my items.
That's kind of blowing my mind that I didn't do that.
Yeah, this is the one that's causing everything to go wrong, you know?
Ah!
That was so bad.
I hate myself.
Just kill them fast.
Good.
Twelve coins is decent.
What in the box?
Do I want a following familiar with the randomized appearance, fire rate, damage, and bonus tier effects?
Maybe I do.
Or I wait until I can make it free.
I can also buy this battery later, but I'm going to wait a bit because I have two charges left.
It will be a waste.
Not bad.
Ah!
Almost perfect.
That was nearly perfection.
Wait, wait.
I'm not going to go in there yet.
If I go in there, I want to go in with a full charge on my thingy, of course.
We also have a hundred percent demon chance, which means we need to go in there with a full coupon.
Oh!
I stole my battery!
God damn it.
I'm just killing myself.
Hey, money.
Yeah, suddenly my chances of winning this are very slim.
Very low HP.
Uh, let's go back to the shop now that we have battery.
Or charge, I mean.
Okay.
I mean.
That's fine.
Uh, let me do this again, then.
Oh, you know what?
I should...
Hold on a minute.
I just realized the strategy I can do here.
Check it out.
This will remain open.
I get the devil deal.
I use my charge.
I come back here.
I do it again.
Holy shit.
Ooh, that's massive, actually.
Let's not die now, please.
Oh!
I'm just killing fast.
Sick.
Sulfur, I'm not even...
I don't even want that, honestly.
But I guess I'll pick it up just to get the one out of three on Leviathan.
So check it out.
We're gonna go in here.
Okay.
Monster manual.
Oh, god.
Stop that.
Imagine I accidentally walk into that one.
That's two out of three on Bookworm.
Yes, we'll do this.
Gonna go out now?
Because it's gonna remain open?
Yes.
Back to the shop, baby.
Dude, why?
Hit it, for fuck's sake.
Why is that so difficult?
Okay.
Uh, yeah.
Go back and use this now.
We do have an issue with HP.
I mean, we have a couple lives, but HP is an issue right now.
This is so good.
Oh, beautiful.
What a play.
Although I will say getting extra damage right now is not actually that beneficial.
My damage is good.
What I need is survival.
Yppikak is taking care of my damage, right?
Imagine I find Pyromaniac.
Holy shit.
That would be the ultimate dream.
I'm not gonna go in there.
I will destroy these mushrooms.
Sometimes there's an insane mushroom item you can get from these.
Speak enough.
It's not that one.
It's another one.
Let's see if I can do this.
Okay, I'm not gonna risk it again.
Box can be opened with bombs.
I mean, I have four keys, but I really do like my current one.
Soul hearts, black hearts, and bone hearts?
What the fuck are bone hearts?
Is that a spelling error?
Like, I've never seen that.
Maybe I haven't unlocked it yet or something.
Kill him.
Goodbye.
Yeah, I think we're done here.
I wanna see a bone heart.
I wish for a bone heart.
I think I'll take this as well, actually.
Or... wait, let me think.
Yeah.
I take that.
Why not?
No!
I misclicked!
I accidentally misclicked my keyboard.
It happened.
It's fine.
Going here.
Okay, so next one is Mom.
We cannot lose HP on this one now, man.
I'm telling you.
Oh, no.
It's Mom.
Come on, show me your feet.
Good, good, good.
Ooh, I did it.
I can't lose this black heart.
I feel like I need it.
Yes.
I'm so proud of myself.
That was so systematic, man.
This is how I need to play.
Okay, these guys are dangerous.
No!
Fuck.
God, I hate these guys, man.
I hate them.
I can't believe that just happened.
It's fine.
Just focus.
We can do it.
Oh, but I don't have any red hearts.
I want to find a treasure room so I can actually use this coupon.
I did it!
No!
God, this is...
I'm so bad at this.
No more mistakes.
Okay, we gained battery there.
Wait, isn't that... Look at my follower.
It looks like the Mega Man that can transform or whatever.
Oh, shit.
No, those early to...
Did that door just close on me?
Wait, hold on a minute.
Taking... You know what we're gonna do?
We're actually gonna make a separate list for this because I'm losing my mind.
I can't take it anymore.
We're gonna... We're gonna do... Let me see.
Fight room.
Oops.
Taking damage... Closes the gates.
And also, we know this.
For some reason, destroying mushroom opened gates.
Some... I can't think of anything else right now, but those are the two.
We're gonna keep making notes on this.
And when we have enough, it's gonna make sense.
We're just gonna collect data pretty much.
Think about it like that.
Okay, so one and a half hearts.
I'm tempted to destroy this whole room just to find items.
But there's a pretty high chance I kill myself.
So we're gonna just not go ahead and do that.
Okay, that was good.
Let's go this way.
Oh my god.
I hate when they jump.
Oish!
Yeah, you saw the diagonal there?
That was nice.
Now where do we have a treasure room?
Yes!
That's huge for me.
I will use my coupon, man.
I just need one treasure room.
That's fine.
What a shot!
Why do I always start to play way better when I suddenly have no HP?
Isaac gets bigger.
I don't like that.
That's bad for me.
Blackheart is massive.
I definitely exchanged a key for this.
You would be crazy not to do it.
So we have the boss here.
Still no treasure room.
I think it's worth it to go in now since I have the Blackheart.
If I lose it, I'm gonna deal damage, right?
Chariot, baby!
Oh, I was hoping I could shoot while I'm doing this so I can be immune to my own bombs.
Oh no.
I need to focus here.
Oh my god.
Oh.
Wow.
Kill him.
Fuck!
No!
Actually, we're fine.
We have two hearts.
Yeah!
Damage and shot speed.
See, this is kind of useless for me.
Actually, not that useless, but a little bit.
So check it out.
We're gonna do the same thing.
I'm gonna go in there.
We're gonna use the coupon, right?
Actually, I may as well take this.
We're gonna use the coupon.
Let's see what's in there.
Well, there we go.
It's only one item.
Contract from below.
Increases the likelihood of a room clear reward.
Call me crazy, but this item is actually bad.
I feel like I would rather have a room clear reward than the chance of a...
Oh, actually, wait a minute.
No, mathematically, it's actually better.
I just realized.
Yeah, because 33...
Yeah, I understand.
I can't believe I never sat down and just thought about that for a bit.
Okay, we're not moving on yet.
Treasure room is calling.
There goes one of my black hearts.
We got battery again.
Is there even a shot here?
Oh, that was risky.
That was risky.
Get away from me.
I knew that was gonna go bad.
I felt it in my bones.
Hey, we actually nailed it.
Oh, one thing I didn't do yet, I need to look for secrets.
Since I have bombs, right?
There's nothing in there.
Well, there you go.
Look at that.
Okay, I really need to find more HP.
Somehow.
Just kill them fast while they're stacked.
See, how did that damage me?
I was out of range, I'm pretty sure.
I guess I wasn't.
I would say we're done here.
Totally just wasted two hearts on this.
And no treasure room?
I don't understand that.
Oh, wait a minute.
We're in a challenge.
That's probably what it is.
Oh, man.
I keep falling for that crap.
No.
Okay.
It's time for Mom.
We can't make mistakes now.
This needs to be on point.
I'll be back.
Duh!
Fuck, guys, I think I'm done.
I'm gonna die here.
I should be looking for secrets, man.
As I go along.
Maybe there's healing in there.
There's battery.
Oh, nice.
That's huge.
I only have three keys.
Oh, I should be bombing this wall, actually.
Okay.
Clear.
Nothing there.
This room.
Let's blow it all up.
I'm really trying not to kill myself right now.
Good aim.
Okay, I think I want to give this guy some coins.
No.
Yes.
Just a couple.
I think we're not gonna find any more...
I was about to say we're not gonna find any more shops, but that's not the case.
This is still shop territory.
Ooh, that's massive!
Oh, my God.
Will you please give me more?
I mean, okay, that's fine, too.
Dude!
Run is saved.
Dog food, put it in my tummy.
Holy shit, that was good.
Nailed that.
Calm down, sir.
Wow, that almost hit me.
I gotta be more careful.
Fuck you.
Clean.
Dude, coupon time!
Are you ready?
Wait, let me do this first.
Oh, my God!
We're totally back.
Mom's box.
Lock spots a trinket, doubles the effects of the trinkets.
Ooh, that could be really good with Mom's pearl.
Right?
15?
Okay, you ready?
Here we go.
We're gonna buy this battery and do it again.
Yeah!
Triggers the teleport 2.0 effect each time an active item is used.
Wait, I don't...
Hmm.
I don't think I want that.
That sounds scary.
Also, it's gonna re- yeah, okay, I thought it wasn't a trinket, but that's okay.
I'm taking this.
I should also buy this, actually.
Dude, we are so back!
Holy crap!
I thought we were done for, but now...
We're so back.
Fuck!
Oh my god.
This room is insane.
What?!
We're dead.
It's over.
It's actually over.
This room was crazy.
How can anyone do that without taking damage, man?
Maybe if you had the laser.
Okay, keys.
I'll take those.
Ooh, that was so good.
So satisfying.
Dude,
some enemies you just nail with this attack, you know?
Other enemies, not so much.
I think I should go back to the shop and keep couponing.
We also have a battery in that big room.
Wait, 100% demon mode.
Dude, we're gonna do the play again.
The demon play.
And maybe we find more batteries as well.
This guy has a lot of HP.
Nice!
Double trouble there, opening the wall and everything.
Okay, we're gonna save that, of course.
We're not taking that yet.
Dude, I'm gonna call it now.
We actually got this in the bag.
I'm telling you.
Beautiful shot.
We're even gonna go in there.
Grab this stuff.
Yeah, go in here.
Oh my god.
What was that?
Freaking frisbee!
How do you do this?
You can't do this.
Whoa!
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
Bomb here?
Yep.
Oh my god, we're actually so back.
Dude, this run is a roller coaster for me.
It's up and down, constantly.
Oh, I also just realized we still have two lives.
So we're actually kind of chilling.
I swear to god, these spiders.
Okay.
We got them.
Let me see if this is a real battery.
It is a real battery.
That's good news.
It means our play can still work.
But we gotta find the boss.
Also, we're still at 100% demon.
Okay, these guys don't shoot.
Go!
Wish me luck!
Shit, it's Mom!
And you like that, Mom?
You like that, Mom?
Whoa!
Oh my god.
Okay, that's good.
Dodge that one.
Dude, I'm killing it.
It's actually no problem.
Easy dodge.
Yeah, you're dead.
You're dead.
I got you.
Beautiful.
Wait, it was a fake one.
I was about to say I have 100% demon, but there's no demon.
Oh wait, I have 100% demon because I have the 100% demon mode.
Right!
I was wondering why it was at 100% so much.
It makes sense.
No, wait, this is not a second boss.
I'm actually so confused right now.
I'm not even kidding.
Like this...
Sponsor...
Ooh, dude, we should actually take that.
Three out...
Wait, how does that work with my bombs?
Am I gonna shoot two bombs at a time?
Tears and shot speed applies fear to enemies include...
Ooh, that could be good, actually.
I like both.
Let's just...
Nice.
Okay, so can I even go back?
Fuck, I can't go back.
The battery strategy.
I can't afford to lose more HP.
I can't do this.
I have to go.
Wait, what was this one?
The Book of Sin sponsor?
Oh, I should actually use that.
Dude!
Are you ready?
Ah, but wait, I can't do it.
I need the coupon on me.
Oh, wait, that's an active.
This is not an active.
We're totally chilling.
Who is the man?
I am.
And now we go back.
And because we know it's going to stay open, Bob's your uncle.
This is fantastic.
I'm so proud of myself.
Yep.
Boom.
I'm so proud of myself.
Got them both for free.
And this one we used, so we just move on.
Coupon, coupon.
I'm so happy.
Okay.
Now, see, this door is open now.
I'm just going to note down everything.
I don't care.
Spawn in Yudero.
Door Fight Club.
Oh, I guess this is Fight Club section, so I'm just going to write.
Gates open.
I don't know why, it's just open.
When we get enough data points, we're going to understand why this is.
Okay, this is going to be easy.
Oh, no.
Okay, we're fine.
Nailed them.
Dude, the fear is already working.
I actually feel so confident.
I think we got this in the bag.
Yeah, I shot two bombs there, you saw that?
Masterful dodging as well.
Okay.
Yo, the fact that we can see the entire layout is crazy to me.
I'm going to go ahead and say the boss is going to be right below me south.
It's right below me south, in the very end.
Let's go this way.
Holy shit!
All right.
We're totally back!
Thank you, game.
I appreciate it.
I will destroy all of these little X-Acts now.
That's right.
Everything dies.
Almost killed myself.
Cuking at me.
Wait, how did he just die?
Kill the tomatoes.
We don't like your kind here.
Oh my... wait, what's happening here?
Why am I being blessed?
That was crazy.
I can't lose.
That's fine, it happens.
Okay, so this is not the boss.
But it was a boss, right?
Kill the small ones.
That was such good maneuvering.
Wait, where did that come from?
Is that me making that happen?
Okay.
Look for secrets as well, do not forget.
Beautiful... I mean, how good am I?
Okay, let's pay attention now.
First we destroy all this.
We're gonna do the same thing with these now.
We're gonna note everything down.
So, hold on.
One, two, three, four, four, six.
Six, twelve, eighteen.
Twenty-two.
Twenty-two items.
Eighteen, twenty-one, eight.
Stats, um...
Okay, here we go.
Nothing.
I don't understand what the fuck that means.
It may actually be a bigger mystery than the frickin' Fight Club doors.
I need to use my coupon.
The thing is though, there's no shops here, right?
So...
I'm gonna say...
We're gonna get a demon.
And we're gonna use it there, again and again.
Oh, God.
How am I so bad?
Okay.
Some of these release shots when they die.
Careful.
I mean, who knows?
Maybe two more Soul Hearts are gonna fall out, right?
Oh, no.
Okay, I don't know.
We may actually be dead.
If we don't find more Soul Hearts, you know?
It's not looking good.
We gotta find the boss.
Fast.
No!
I knew that was gonna happen.
Yeah!
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Thank you, Flies.
They actually just saved me.
Imagine I one-shot this challenge, dude.
That would be crazy.
There we go.
Take you out.
I wonder if there's a way in the game to sort of remove an item that you have, you know?
Like, maybe there's an item you pick up and it's like, oh, randomly remove an item from your pool or something.
Watch this.
Oh, that's nice.
Please, please, please.
Yes!
Could've been a black card.
Oh, again?
Dude!
We're back.
We're actually back.
Uh, let's keep looking for secrets.
Maybe over here.
Wait, the boss is here.
Uh, I think we go.
I don't see any batteries on the map, but that's okay.
Daddy Long Legs.
Oh, you're gonna die, son.
You ain't nothing!
Okay, he's gonna do that stuff now.
That's cool.
That's for you.
Oh my god, nearly hit myself.
Dude, no problem.
Boom, baby!
You suck!
Uh, oh wait, we're not done.
And there we go, more healing.
Huge.
And then, oh, we're gonna go in here.
I don't care about that.
I do care about this.
Let's see.
Fuck.
I mean, this is good.
I'll come back with more battery.
Yep.
I shall be back.
This is the most optimized freaking gameplay you've ever seen.
I'm not gonna waste any hearts on this.
We're gonna do this so efficiently.
We're gonna look for secrets.
All of that.
Uh, yeah, down here.
Okay.
How did I almost mess that up?
That was so easy.
Oh wait, this is my creep.
It's good creep.
I'm not gonna step today.
But I will check out the walls.
They also throw bombs.
I wonder if there's only one secret.
When you do a challenge.
Or maybe it is really random.
Uh, I don't think we can find a battery, unfortunately.
Yeah.
The thing is though, am I gonna go ahead and sacrifice one HP for this?
I mean, my damage is good, right?
I don't really need this.
Then again, I am, you know, pretty scared of just dying instantly to some bullshit.
This helps with that.
No, actually, this is bad for me.
Because I shoot so slow.
Chances of getting one of these is gonna be super low.
Especially because look, we have minus two luck.
And this one increases with luck, right?
So fuck this.
Nope.
I'm so proud of myself for that.
Amazing.
The final stage.
Yudero 2.
Uh, I'm gonna go towards this way.
I like that.
Oh my god.
I almost killed myself again.
Freaking tomatoes, man.
Let's try not...
Okay, from now on, in this level, I'm not gonna take any damage.
After this room, I'm not gonna take any damage.
What?
He was following me!
Okay, from now on, no damage.
Oh!
Wait, why is this happening?
Only one door open, though.
Hmm.
Okay.
Whoa, what's this?
Oh, I don't look...
I don't like that.
Fuck.
Oh, this...
Dude, I'm gonna die.
I'm gonna die.
Here, eat that.
No, I'm gonna...
No, there's no way I'm dying here.
Also, I have two lives!
Let's not forget.
Should I be blowing everything up here?
I think so.
Who knows, you know?
Maybe there's two Soul Hearts hiding in there.
Show me the good stuff.
Really?
Nothing?
Okay.
Wait, two!
What does that mean?
Uh, let's see here.
Cards...
Dice room.
We roll all items.
Okay, so we don't know what it is.
Oh, this is scary.
This could fuck me up.
We're gonna see, we're gonna see.
Fuck it, we're doing it.
Okay, this looks good.
Nothing changed there.
What happened?
I don't know.
Something... it was shaking and then it turned all dark.
What the hell, man?
There goes my heart.
Whoa, the boss is here.
Okay, we're gonna go for it.
Are you ready?
This is it.
Wish me luck.
It lifts.
Not for long.
Oh my god.
What?
Die, motherfucker.
Okay, eyes are gone.
It's easy now.
Jesus!
We're dead, we're dead!
We gotta kill the little guys.
Come on.
Haha.
Blow him up, blow him up, blow him up!
Wait, we're not done?
What do you mean?
What do you mean we're not... wait, what?
I thought that was it?
No!
Wait, Satanic Bible.
Activating this before defeating the current floor's boss will replace the boss's reward with a devil deal item that causes health to claim.
Hmm.
Maybe.
Ooh, conjoined?
Two out of three?
Shit.
I don't know, maybe I keep this actually.
I mean, we're approaching the end, right?
Activating this before defeating... so...
Oh, plus one Black Heart on use, yo!
Dude.
This could be massive.
If we manage to, you know, not die.
I mean.
I really want to take this as well.
But maybe I go back and find batteries.
Yeah, cause I can keep moving.
Yeah.
Dude, I'm actually gonna go back and find battery.
Yeah, this is the plan.
Wish me luck.
Oh god.
I can't take damage now.
Oh fuck!
Oh my god.
It's okay.
I
don't know.
Solid.
Very nice.
I need an arcade, man.
I'm rich.
Wait.
It's gonna be easy.
There we go, okay.
Nice.
Oh shit.
Ooh!
Dude, I'm nearly dead.
I don't need all this money.
It's actually over.
Why am I gonna die with so much money in my pocket, man?
Wait, we have a healing here.
But that's not gonna help me, because everything does one health of damage now.
I'm dead!
I can't do that room.
Jesus.
Oh!
We have battery.
I almost blew myself up with a bomb.
I'm going back.
Actually, there's a bunch of poop in here.
This could be health.
Why am I thrown so far?
Okay, you know what?
No, no, no.
It's too risky.
We go back.
Man, 4 HP and we're moving up into heaven?
I don't know if I can do that.
So wait, what does conjoin do?
Oh, fuck.
We're dead.
It's over.
Oh, man.
Okay, we need to use this liberally.
And we need to re- hold on.
Oh, we're fucked.
We need to kill enemies before they get close.
This is the only way.
I really need to lock in here.
Okay, hold on.
Last sip of the coffee.
Come on.
I think the boss is somewhere up north.
Jesus Christ.
What is happening in this room?
Oh, there's fire!
I'm going to die in here.
It's over.
I can't go in there.
Kill him!
No!
We're alive!
Oh my god, the fires.
Get- space invaders.
Yes, yes!
Fuck you!
Oh my god.
Dude, we're actually so back.
I'm going to destroy this fire.
Wait, I need to make sure I can't kill myself, so if I do it here, I should be okay.
Lovely.
And we'd use this.
Fuck you.
I killed myself, or I hurt myself.
Isaac gets bigger?
No, I don't want that.
You crazy?
I can't believe we're back.
I'm not going to sell the skin before we shoot the bear, though.
Another heart!
Massive.
Just kill them fast.
Wow.
Dude, I have 81 coins.
Can I spend them, please, on something?
Oh, what is this?
Kill them!
Kill them fast!
Somehow.
Some way.
Okay.
Go this way.
Not falling for your shit?
Oh, I did.
I fell for it.
The boss is here.
Guys.
This may be it.
Okay.
I'm ready.
Let's go.
Isaac!
You're mine!
Oh.
Whoa.
Lock in, lock in, lock in, lock in.
That's fine.
We're chilling.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on.
Yep, yep.
Oh, it's easy.
You're mine, bitch.
Your cheeks belong to me.
Easy.
There we fucking go.
First tried it.
Oh.
I can't believe it.
Wait, we just unlocked something else from that.
Let me actually look at that.
Items.
Dude.
I almost found everything.
Look at this.
Whoa.
Okay, wait a minute.
Never mind.
Holy shit.
Look at that!
I forgot how many pages there was.
What the fuck?
Fuck.
By the way, of all of these items, this is the worst.
I think.
Of all of these, it may be the worst item.
I really wish it would show me the last one I unlocked.
Oh well.
That's gonna be it.
What a great way to end that, huh?
I think that was great.
What a way to end that one.
What do you think of that, huh?
That run was over so many times, guys.
And then it wasn't.
It was a crazy roller coaster.
Holy shit.
It was rage maxing.
No, man.
It was not.
Maybe it was.
Not intentionally, though.
Guppy color, 50%, clutched.
Oh yeah.
Definitely.
But I actually had one more after that.
That's scripted rage fades.
Yeah, indeed.
Scripted bait maxing.
The realization with conjoined.
You know what's funny?
Right when I picked up conjoined and I asked myself what it was, I actually remembered.
I didn't even think about it until I had it.
Because I remembered in that moment that it was like a triple shot.
531.
Holy shit.
Yeah, 530 viewers.
What's up, guys?
Why are there so many viewers?
That's way above average.
Oliver's the suicide king.
For sure.
We had a rate.
Really?
Who rated?
Let me see.
How can I see that?
I need to filter.
Blue SR.
Rated with a party of 1,300 viewers.
Holy shit.
Hold on.
I need to do the shout out thing.
There
we go.
Thank you, Blue SR.
I don't know if you're here.
I don't know when you rated, but...
Oh, 44 minutes ago I see it.
Thank you so much, man.
Sorry I didn't see that when you did it.
I was in the middle of a run and I don't look at chat while I play.
Thank you so much.
Blue SR.
At the start of the stream you said we're just gonna chill and the end was crazy.
That's what's happening with this game, you know?
Like, I was so locked in during that last challenge that I was just...
forgetting the fact that I was sick, you know?
Well, I don't want to say I'm sick.
I'm like, I'm just feeling a little down under, right?
At least Blue brought his chat in for the funniest run, I guess.
So, yeah.
The other ones were kind of disastrous, for sure.
The break or stream is over.
I'm gonna end it here, for sure.
I'm gonna say a bit though in chat, just for a couple minutes more.
I think for sure that me feeling a little down definitely affected my first runs.
I was not feeling too great, you know?
But when the game throws me one of those runs where it's so exciting, I can't not log in.
This challenge is hard, right?
I thought it was.
But it was also super fun.
I love you doing big damage, but also having big chances of taking big damage.
The riskiness is exciting.
I wonder why you hate...
Okay, it's not because I hate Lazarus.
It's because Lazarus is right next to Azazel.
So every time I end up getting Lazarus when I pick random, I thought for a brief second that I was gonna get Azazel and then I get disappointed right after.
That's why I sound disappointed, okay?
It's not because I hate Lazarus, it's just because I could have had Azazel.
That's the thing.
Lazarus is fine.
I don't mind.
I think you're destined to roll Eve 90% of the time.
So I'm not crazy, right?
I feel like I get her a lot.
You're so Azazel-filled, how can you not be?
Every time I don't play Azazel, I wish I was playing Azazel.
Everything feels just worse on every other character.
I am the number one Azazel fan.
Dude, give me Azazel and a converter and I can make anything happen.
I can solve world hunger with those two.
It kind of gets boring after a while, not for me.
I love it.
I can't get enough.
I think you actually have zero wins with Magdalene?
Really?
I think I have one win.
I seem to remember a good run with her.
Where I was healing a lot, or was that someone else?
Maybe it was someone else.
That Eden run was so bad, I agree.
It was not good.
But what about that run where I went stepping?
Like, that had so much promise.
And then the freaking bombs came out.
That was so anticlimactic, I was so sad after that, man.
It showed so much promise and it was so much fun and then it just ended, you know?
We can do a poll next time to pick a challenge, for sure.
That sounds good.
Give them a demon and a device that turns your soul into flesh.
I mean, the reason I say that is because Azazel starts with the black hearts, right?
You can turn them into red hearts, which is amazing.
The biggest drawback of Azazel is his black hearts.
So being able to turn those into red hearts is just unbelievable.
The best combo ever, in my opinion.
All chat just wants you to do semi-speedrun.
I mean, okay, we're going to do speedruns next time.
Let's say that.
I enjoy those a lot, actually.
Those are fun.
Next time is going to be the speedrun stream.
Let's say that, okay?
I'm going to write it down as well, just so you don't think I'm going to forget.
To-do list...
Oh, I also forgot about reading my to-do list this time.
I forgot about this part.
Bethany's calling.
Next stream...
Massive speed.
Want to see more hush?
Yeah, we definitely do that.
I mean, I will play everything, don't worry.
It's just going to take a while.
Are you completing challenges in order, or have you picked them?
Or have you picked some with good unlocks?
I'm just going in order, actually.
But I'm not against just picking a challenge that sounds fun.
It's just been satisfying to cross them off 1 after 1, right?
But I can definitely do other challenges, especially if we do a poll on it.
Then for sure, yeah.
We're going to do a random challenge.
We can even do, like, a dice throw between 1 and, I don't know, 20 or so, and then pick the number on the list or something.
Oh yeah, check recent unlocks for... or you can see that in Steam achievements, that's true.
Let me see.
Suicide King unlocked a new item.
Little chat, that's the new item.
Everything is terrible, too.
Reed just got harder?
No.
Canehold's paperclip unlocked a new starting item.
Key Bum unlocked a new item, and then Wooden Cross is also a new item.
Oh, Abaddon is a new item.
I had that last time, I think.
And Rune of Perthrow is also unlocked.
That was last time.
Yeah, that was everything from last time.
Today I only got 2 achievements.
Everything
is terrible, too.
The sequel is out.
It's even worse now.
Do you think at some point you may look up some of the more obscure secrets or unlocks?
Some are basically impossible, too.
Blind?
I like that.
Maybe.
Who knows?
Maybe at the end we're going to do a wrap-up stream, just like Minecraft.
But I think probably not.
I kind of like having this game just be a game that I can play whenever and have these secrets in it that I don't know what are, you know?
It kind of makes it more mysterious.
I think that's kind of fun.
But maybe.
We'll see.
Depends how I feel at the end.
LacyMadManCoop?
I don't know what that means.
Is that a challenge?
There's only a handful of things you can't do blind.
You're good.
Okay, perfect.
Well, there we go.
Oh, you're talking about multiplayer.
So that's what multiplayer is.
Just go in together and blow shit up.
That actually sounds like fun.
YouTuber?
That's so funny.
My Nick in the past used to be MediMan.
Almost exactly the same then.
Like, what's up with that?
Destined.
Big Isaac YouTuber, okay.
I don't think I could do the thing with one game, man.
Like, you know how there's Minecraft YouTubers and Noita YouTubers and Isaac and all that?
How do you... I guess you gotta be really good at the game, you know?
I think it would get tired of one game, like, forever.
Just makes you realize how deep those games are, you know?
When there's people who have entire channels dedicated to them.
Like Minecraft.
Like, that game is deep.
You don't have to be good.
Okay.
Yes, 5,000 hours?
Jesus Christ.
I mean, I shouldn't be saying that.
I mean, if I think of World of Warcraft, I have way more than 5,000 hours.
Wait, how many days is that?
Let me see.
208 days.
Okay.
I definitely have more hours than World of Warcraft.
Or days.
I think I have, like, 1.5 years in game in World of Warcraft.
If you combine it all throughout time...
Meow for us?
I'm not gonna do that, I'm sorry.
Not right now.
Maybe I'll bring in Jackie for that.
Or if I play Mugenics, I'm gonna Meow.
You have 10,000 hours on Lost Ark.
Wow.
Dude, that is actually crazy, because that game has not been out for that long, right?
World of Warcraft has been out for quite a while.
Lost Ark is not that old, is it?
Or maybe it is.
40, dude.
Damn.
I mean, a lot of that must have been just, like, AFK-ing then, or...
Just all tapping out or something.
Right, the Meow's Patreon exclusive.
Also, why is the chat font doesn't show caps?
It only shows caps.
That's the point.
It's to match the background style, you know?
It's just a stylistic thing.
It's on purpose.
I don't know what next stream is.
I hope I feel better tomorrow.
I hope this doesn't devolve into an actual sickness, because that would suck.
So, I'm not sure.
When I know, I'm going to put it on Discord events and Twitch events.
But sometimes I also do them out of the blue, like today, you know?
I wasn't sure.
I was feeling kind of shit this morning, but I really wanted to play, so...
It could happen out of the blue, as well.
I was feeling the Isaac... what do you call it?
When you're addicted, you know?
I got the Shakes.
Down with the sickness.
Yeah, yeah.
Thank you, Avitus.
Alright, guys, thank you so much for watching.
I'm going to leave.
I'm going to make some soup, I think.
Or maybe order some, because I don't really feel like making some.
And thank you to Blue Senior for rating me.
I don't think you're here, but thank you very much.
I appreciate that.
That means a lot.
Thanks, everybody.
I'll see you around.
Bye-bye.